[
    {
        "question": "😈🗡",
        "answer": "demon slayer"
    },
    {
        "question": "🐰👧👨‍👧",
        "answer": "bunny girl senpai"
    },
    {
        "question": "💀📃",
        "answer": "death note"
    },
    {
        "question": "1️⃣🧩",
        "answer": "one piece"
    },
    {
        "question": "1️⃣👊👨",
        "answer": "one punch man"
    },
    {
        "question": "🏹❌🏹",
        "answer": "hunter x hunter"
    },
    {
        "question": "🐲🔮",
        "answer": "dragon ball"
    },
    {
        "question": "😡😴🏀",
        "answer": "slam dunk"
    },
    {
        "question": "🦔🔵🏃🏻",
        "answer": "sonic"
    },
    {
        "question": "🕵️💊➞👶🏻",
        "answer": "detective conan"
    },
    {
        "question": "🏰💨",
        "answer": "howl's moving castle"
    },
    {
        "question": "💦🌎🔥🌬",
        "answer": "avatar the last airbender"
    },
    {
        "question": "🍎🧺",
        "answer": "fruits basket"
    },
    {
        "question": "🦸‍♂️🦹‍♀️🏫",
        "answer": "my hero academia"
    }
]